Speaker 1: Hey all, Peter Zion here, coming to let you know that our next question time is going to be on
Speaker 1: February 7th. Question time is when you get a question, this guy in person. So February 7th,
Speaker 1: noon Eastern, or 9 a.m. Pacific, if you prefer. If you are an analyst member of our Patreon system,
Speaker 1: send in your questions now so I can cram for the test. If you are not an analyst member,
Speaker 1: now it might be a great time to upgrade or join, because as we do with every question time,
Speaker 1: you have the ability to book now, in which case every dime of your subscription fee that would
Speaker 1: normally come to me for the entire month of January, February, and March will instead go to a charity,
Speaker 1: specifically the Los Angeles Food Bank system. The LA Food Bank has been providing assistance to Los
Speaker 1: Angelinos for over 40 years, but more than that, you have probably heard about the disastrous fires
Speaker 1: that have hit the region in recent weeks. Specifically, we have seen the greatest amount
Speaker 1: of damage in absolute terms to any American metro ever, and arguably the greatest in relative terms
Speaker 1: to any American metro since the dawn of the Industrial Age. So please, please, please join,
Speaker 1: please, please, please give if you can. And if for whatever reason you think an organization that
Speaker 1: gives 20% of their efforts to miners, it's just your cup of tea, think about yourself. Los Angeles is
Speaker 1: also home to the port of LA and Long Beach, which is the country's largest container port. And if the
Speaker 1: damage gets much worse in Los Angeles, the port will shut down, and we will all be feeling the pain
Speaker 2: a lot more than the $15 a month that the analyst fee for the Patreon page costs you. See you on the 7th.
Thank you.